Hello everyone, I'm Chatty Charlie.
Let's practise some informal phrases in English!
Yes!
What is it?
Look!
Yay! Our team won!
You can use 'Look!'
when you want to direct someone's attention to something.
Did you see the score? 12 – 0.
Yeah! That's crazy!
You can use 'That's crazy!'
when you want to say something seems unbelievable.
Shall we watch the tennis match after school?
Why not?
You can use 'Why not?'
when you want to agree with a suggestion.
Watching this match is boring.
It's more fun to play tennis.
Well! What are we waiting for?
Let's go play tennis ourselves.
You can use 'What are we waiting for?'
when you want to say that you should do something immediately.
Oh, no! We need tickets to see the basketball game tonight!
I can buy them online.
Got them!
You can say 'Got them!'
when you've completed an action.
Let's practise.
I'll say something and you respond
using one of the Everyday English phrases.
It's so hot today!
Oh, look!
We can get an ice cream.
What are we waiting for?
I can't find my dog.
Where is he?
Look!
Hey! I've got two tickets to the rugby match tomorrow!
Want to come with me?
Why not?
Wow! Did you see that?
That's crazy!
Have you booked the seats for the basketball game?
Got them!
After this video,
think of five more situations
and test your partner.
Remember, practice makes perfect!